http://pcbdb.net/office/policy.html

BROWSE
FORUM | Your Annoucements | General Discussion | Wanted | Name That Game
| Technical Support
| PCBdB* Annoucements
(What?)
Remember me
Cannot access? | Use?
Create an account now!
Zero spam tolerance
We do not tolerate spam and will never sell, rent, lease or give away your information (name, address, email, etc.) to any third party. Nor will we send you unsolicited email.
Our site's registration form requires users to give us just the basic contact information (i.e., email address). This is used to restore your password if lost or forgotten.
How do we protect your information?
In order to prevent unauthorized access, PCBdB* uses strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given to us. We take all reasonable precautions to ensure the security of personal data stored on our system.
All your personal information is password-protected - only registered users have access to their own information. As a registered user, you will be able to edit or delete your personal information details at any time using your own username and password.
Does PCBdB* share information?
Your personal information is being provided only to PCBdB* unless we specifically state otherwise. We will not disclose your personally identifiable information to any person or company except where you have given us permission to do so or if the law requires it, or where in good faith PCBdB* believes such action is necessary to comply with a legal process.
What About Cookies?
Cookies are pieces of information that an interactive service (e.g. website, digital TV) transfers to your hardware (e.g. computer, set-top box, etc.) for recordkeeping purposes. PCBdB* may use cookies where appropriate. If you are using a computer and do not wish to receive cookies you can switch them off on the browser on your computer. But in that case some of our functions may not work as usual.
Choice/Opt-out
If you would like to be removed from our database or mailing list, please let us know.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us.
Copyright© PCBdB* 2006,2007,2008,2009,2010,2011. All Rights Reserved.
All names and images used are trademarked by their respective trademark holders. PCBdB* takes no responsibility for the content of any linked websites.
Designed and coded by iZ Group
This web site is optimized for 1024x768 pixel or bigger resolution.
HOME | ABOUT | CONTACT | REPORT | COPYRIGHTS | PRIVACY POLICY | TERM OF USE
